Finding Aid for Jens Jensen Drawings and Papers 1903-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Drawings
  - K
    - Keehn, Roy D., Lake Bluff, Illinois
      - A topographic survey of a portion of the estate of Mr. Roy T.[sic] Keehn. Telegraph Road..., 1929; KEE2; Green, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; location, type of trees; unsigned; 68 x 63 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 52)
    - Kelley, Phelps, Lake Bluff, Illinois
      - A planting plan for the estates of Messrs. Phelps and Russell Kelley, 1926; KEH1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; driveways, pools, gardens, arbors; notes; signed; 87 x 59 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 52)
        (neg. # JEN-Keh-1)
      - Plans of Residence, 1926; KEH2; Blueprint; north, south elevations, sections; unsigned; 95 x 75 cm; No scale (Map-case 54, Folder 52)
      - Plans of residence, 1926; KEH3; Blueprint, yellow, black pencil; first floor plan; unsigned; 95 x 75 cm; Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 54, Folder 52)
      - Plan of residence, 1926; KEH4; Blueprint; east, west elevations; unsigned; 95 x 75 cm; Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 54, Folder 52)
    - Kelley, William V., Lake Forest, Illinois (Howard Van Doren Shaw, architect)
      - Property of Wm. V. Kelley, Esq. Plan of topo. survey, 1913; KEL1; Red, black ink on linen; distances, elevations; notes; location of plantings; note: ""Tile laid 1917 by A.G.S.""; signed; 115 x 80 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # JEN-Kel-1)
      - A topographical survey for the estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1913; KEL2; Red, black ink on linen; elevations; unsigned; 103 x 75 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley. Plan of proposed improvement, showing building sites, drives, pond and property divisions, 1914; KEL3; Red, black ink on linen; signed; 112 x 72 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # JEN-Kel-3)
      - Estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley. Grade plan for pond, 1914; KEL4; Red, black ink on linen; existing, proposed contour lines, existing elevations; signed; 71 x 60 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley. Grade plan for pond, #2, 1914; KEL5; Red, black ink on linen; proposed contours; existing, proposed elevations, notes; signed; 78 x 40 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley. Plan for drain tile, 1914; KEL6; Ink on linen; location of tile, distances, elevations; quantities and sizes of tile; signed; 74 x 50 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Planting plan for a portion of the estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley, 1914; KEL7; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings in area of lake; notes; signed; 91 x 79 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # KEL7)
      - Planting plan for a portion of the estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley, 1914; KEL8; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings around lake; many penciled in sections of roadway, gardens, amounts, notes; signed; 83 x 111 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # JEN-Kel-8)
      - Grounds of W.V. Kelly[sic], Esq. Road-drain and water plan, 1915; KEL9; Pencil, red, black ink on tracing paper; residence by Howard Shaw; penciled note at bottom, distinguishing various hatched lines representing water, gas, electricity, etc.; signed; 97 x 47 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Swimming pool detail plans. Estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1916; KEL10; Ink on linen; details of rail, ladder, spring, falls, steps, drainage; plans, cross-sections; signed; 96 x 64 cm; Scales vary (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # KEL10)
      - Water, road, drainage, etc. Estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1916; KEL11; Red, black ink on linen; location of lines; residence by Howard Shaw; unsigned; 128 x 102 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Preliminary sketch for proposed location of farm group and pool. Estate of W.V. Kelley, Esquire, 1917; KEL12; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; signed; 57 x 50 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100'\ (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # JEN-Kel-12)
      - A planting plan for the garden area. Estate of W.V. Kelley, 1917; KEL13; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; pool, footpaths, council ring, gardens; residence by Howard Shaw; signed; 103 x 81 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # JEN-Kel-13)
      - Tennis court location. W.V. Kelley, Esq., 1917; KEL14; ; Pencil on tracing paper; distances, trellis'; cross-section; signed; 27 x 29 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20'; (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Planting plan for vegetable garden. Estate of W.V. Kelley, Esq., 1917; KEL15; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; signed; 102 x 48 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
        (neg. # JEN-Kel-15)
      - Farm buildings for Wm. V. Kelley, Esq., 1922; KEL16; Blueprint; Emil Liska, architect; unsigned; plan of house sketched on verso; 91 x 50 cm; Scale: 1/16"" = 1' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Grading plan for west lake on the estate of Mr. W.V. Kelley, 1922; KEL17; Yellow, black ink on linen; directions for fill and grades; elevations around lake; signed; 47 x 36 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Plan showing tile lines in portion of the estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley lying west of r.r. tracks, 1922; KEL18; Ink on linen; sizes, quantities(in feet) of tiles; unsigned; 44 x 26 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Plan for figuring excavation for the west lake. Estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1922; KEL19; Pencil, yellow, black ink on linen; distances, elevations; unsigned; 108 x 73 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - A preliminary sketch for the stable group. Estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1924; KEL20; Ink on linen; buildings, footpaths; location, type, amounts of plantings; unsigned; 91 x 61 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Topographical plat..., 1925; KEL21; Blueprint; black, pink pencil; drives, gardens, pools drawn in; unsigned; 145 x 83 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Detail of filter installation for the swimming pool. Estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1926; KEL22; Ink on linen; unsigned; 76 x 52 cm; Scales vary (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Plan of filter installation for the swimming pool. Estate of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, 1926; KEL23; Yellow, black ink on linen; similar to KEL22; unsigned; 77 x 63 cm; Scales vary (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - A planting plan for the property of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, lying south of C. & N.W.R.R. and west of Green Bay Road, 1926; KEL24; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; signed; 108 x 81 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - A topo survey for the property of Mr. Wm. V. Kelley, lying south of the C. & N.W.R.R. on Green Bay Road, 1926; KEL25; Green, black ink on linen; topo lines, elevations; unsigned; 109 x 82 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
      - Mr. W.V. Kelley, KEL26; Pencil on tracing paper; note at bottom: ""Plan showing elect. light - telephone - gas lines and locations of hand holes.""; unsigned; 81 x 30 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 53)
    - Kendlville, Indiana. Parks
      - City Park, KEM1; Blueprint, pencil; with location of buildings, topo lines and elevations; unsigned; 27 x 28 cm; Scale: 1"" = 200' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
        (neg. # JEN-Kem-1)
    - Kenilworth, Illinois. Parks., Kenilworth, Illinois
      - Park plan for Kenilworth, Ill., 1909; KEN1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; list of types; signed; 34 x 38 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
        (neg. # KEN1)
      - Plat of survey of Mahony Park, 1933; KEN2; Blueprint; unsigned; 59 x 113 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
        (neg. # KEN2)
      - A wildflower preserve and bird sanctuary for the Mahony Parks, KEN3; Blueline print; aerial sketch; signed; 43 x 31 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
        (neg. # KEN3)
    - Keusink, E.B., Decatur, Illinois
      - Grounds of E.B. Keusink, Esq., 1916; KEU1; Ink on linen; topo lines; locations, type of trees; signed; 70 x 50 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - Kilbourne, L.B., Highland Park, Illinois
      - Plat of survey..., 1905; KIL1; Blueprint; client's name and location in pencil at bottom; unsigned; 76 x 36 cm; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Design for bridge. Grounds of L.B. Kilbourne, 1910; KIL2; Red, black ink on tracing paper; signed; 58 x 34 cm; Scale: 1/2"" = 1' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Revised plan of lake for country home. L.B. Kilbourne, 1910; KIL3; Ink on tracing paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; signed; 38 x 38 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Plan for drainage. Estate of Mr. Kilbourne, 1910; KIL4; Red, black ink on linen; location of tiles, with cross-sections of drive and pool; at lower right, notes in pencil; signed; 110 x 76 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Revised plan for drains. Estate of Mr. Kilbourne, 1910; KIL5; Red, black ink on linen; signed; 110 x 80 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - Kilzinger, Mrs., Glencoe, Illinois
      - Sketch for Mr. Kilzinger, 1925; KIM1; Black, green, orange pencil on tracing paper; plan for gardens, footpath, plantings, arbor; signed; 60 x 73 cm; No scale (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - King, C.L., Lake Forest, Illinois
      - Planting designed for C.L. King, Esq., 1912; KIN1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; perhaps in Jensen's own hand; signed; 65 x 42 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - Klee, Nathan, Highland Park, Illinois (Russel S. Wolcott, architect)
      - Plat of survey, 1924; KLE1; Blueprint, yellow, pink, black pencil; residence, drives, pool, plantings sketched in; unsigned; 52 x 73 cm; No scale (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Proposed residence for Mr. Nathan Klee, 1924; KLE2; 4 sheets, blueprints; first, second floor plans, south elevation, plat plan; Russell S. Walcott, architect; unsigned; 26 x approx. 27 cm; Scales vary (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - First floor plan, 1924; KLE3; Blueprint; direction of prevailing winds indicated; unsigned; 35 x 31 cm; Scale: 1/8"" = 1' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - A planting plan for the grounds of Mr. Nathan Klee, 1926; KLE4; Pencil, yellow, black ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; footpaths, pool; some planting amounts in pencil, and penciled notes; signed; 103 x 76 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
        (neg. # KLE4)
    - Kohn, L., Homewood, Illinois
      - Planting plan. L. Kohn, Esq., 1905; KOH1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; list of types; signed; 58 x 60 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - Kransz, H.P.
      - Plat of grounds of Mr. H.P. Kransz. Sheridan Road and Glenlake Avenue, 1913; KRA1; Ink on linen; outline of residence, walkways, drive; residence by J.A. Nyden; unsigned; 66 x 36 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - Kuppenheimer, Jonas, Lake Forest, Illinois
      - Estate of Jonas Kuppenheimer, Esq....Plan of topo. survey., 1913; KUP1; Ink on linen; elevations, plan of grounds; signed; 118 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Estate of Jonas Kuppenheimer, Esq....Planting plan., 1914; KUP2; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; gardens; signed; 113 x 83 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Plan of new drive and trails for the estate of Jonas Kuppenheimer, Esq., 1916; KUP3; Pencil on tracing paper; plan of estate, with driveways, gardens, views; signed; 120 x 73 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
      - Untitled, KUP4; Ink on linen; topo survey, with elevations, similar to KUP1; unsigned; 122 x 77 cm.; [Scale: 1"" = 30'] (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
    - Kurtzon, Morris, Highland Park, Illinois
      - A topographic survey for the grounds of Mr. Morris Kurtzon, 1924; KUR1; Green, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; unsigned; 113 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 54, Folder 54)
  - L
    - Lackner, F., Kenilworth, Illinois
      - Planting plan for the homes of F. Lackner and C. Corbin, Esq's., 1906; LAC1; Ink on linen; two sheets; 1=location, type, amount of plantings, designated by number; 1a=key to planting numbers; 1, signed; 1a, initialed; 1 = 42 x 49 cm.; 1a = 21 x 29 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
        (neg. # LAC1;)
      - Planting plan for the homes of F. Lackner and C. Corbin, Esq's., 1906; LAC1; Ink on linen; two sheets; 1=location, type, amount of plantings, designated by number; 1a=key to planting numbers; 1, signed; 1a, initialed; 1 = 42 x 49 cm.; 1a = 21 x 29 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
        (neg. # LAC1a)
    - LaGrange, Illinois. Parks.
      - A plat of the site of park no. 1 for the [sic] La Grange Park Board., 1933; LAG1; Yellow, red, black ink on linen; location of drainage, water lines; park divided into sections (red lines), then subdivided and numbered; notes; at lower right, ""section #1""; signed; 126 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - Grading plan for the lagoon and rose garden. Park no. 1. La Grange Park Board., 1933; LAG2; Yellow, black ink on linen; plan, cross-sections; topo. lines; at lower right, ""section #2""; signed; 125 x 86 cm.; Scales vary (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - A planting plan for park no.1. La Grange Park Board., 1932; LAG3; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; footpaths, notes; at lower right, ""section #3""; 126 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - A planting plan for park no. 1. La Grange Park Board., 1933; LAG4; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; footpaths, council ring, steps; notes; at lower right, ""section #4; signed; 125 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - A planting plan for section no. [blank], park no. one. Board of Park Commissions., 1933; LAG5; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; footpaths; notes; at lower right, ""section #5""; signed; 125 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - A planting plan. Section [blank]. La Grange Park Board., 1933; LAG6; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""section #6""; signed; 125 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - A preliminary sketch for park number one. The LaGrange Park Board., 1934; LAG7; Ink on linen; footpaths, trees, lagoon, gardens; signed; 124 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
    - Lake County, Illinois.
      - Plan and profile for the proposed drainage of the East Skokie Valley, 1913; LAK1; Blueprint; indicates property divisions and names of owners; upper left corner torn away; unsigned; 91 x 162 cm.; Scales vary (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - Proposed forest preserves for Lake County, 1919; LAK2; Brown, blue, black ink on tracing paper; layout of preserves; roadways, rail lines, city boundaries; signed; 104 x 101 cm.; Scale: 1 3/4"" = 1 mile (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
      - Northlake. Proposed subdivision.., LAK3; Green, black ink, blue crayon on paper; location of lots, parks, dam, spring; area depicted on Lake Michigan, 1.5 miles from Lake Bluff (south) and North Chicago (north); unsigned; 46 x 19 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
    - Lamborn, William H., Highland Park, Illinois (George W. Maher, architect)
      - Landscape planting design for home grounds of Dr. William H. Lamborn., 1908; LAM1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 88 x 80 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 55)
        (neg. # LAM1)
    - Lasker, Albert D., Glencoe, Illinois (Henry C. Dangler, architect)
      - Grounds of A.D. Lasker, Esq....Planting plan., 1913; LAS1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 61 x 50 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 8' ""Scale not accurate, copied from blueprint."" (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Sketch plan for the estate of Mr. A.D. Lasker., 1915; LAS2; Pencil on tracing paper; signed; 61 x 77 cm.; Scale: 1""= 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Plat of survey., 1916; LAS3; Blueprint; appears to be Lasker property, though note near bottom reads: ""for Hugh T. Birch""; ""A.D. Lasker"" in pencil across bottom of sheet; unsigned; 52 x 48 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - A preliminary sketch for the estate of A.D. Lasker, Esq., 1917; LAS4; Green, black pencil on tracing paper; signed; 110 x 60 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Plot plan for A.D. Lasker, Esq., 1917; LAS5; Pencil on blueprint; some roadways, gardens sketched in; unsigned; 102 x 62 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - A preliminary sketch for the estate of A.D. Lasker, esq....Preliminary sketch No. 3., 1917; LAS6; ; Pencil on tracing paper; signed; 111 x 59 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Elevation of wall at road for Albert D. Lasker, Esq., 1917; LAS7; Blueprint; Henry C. Dangler, architect; unsigned; 140 x 34 cm.; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - A.D. Lasker, 1917; LAS8; Blueprint; elevations of walls; H.C. Dangler, architect; unsigned; 140 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1/8"" = 1' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Plan showing location of gate lodges and wall for A.D. Lasker, Esq., 1917; LAS9; Blueprint; H.C. Dangler, architect; unsigned; 70 x 35 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Plan showing entrances, wall and lodges., 1917; LAS10; Pencil; ""del. F.E.H.""; unsigned; 61 x 27 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - The vegetable garden for the estate of A.D. Lasker., 1917; LAS11; Orange, black pencil on tracing paper; cross-section, plan; unsigned; 92 x 42 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Estate of A.D. Lasker, Esquire. Section I, 1917; LAS12; Pencil on tracing paper; sketch of plantings along entrance drive, lane, greenhouse; upper left corner defaced; signed; 113 x 100 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Grounds of Mr. A.D. Lasker. Facine work on bluff and drainage system adjacent to bluff, 1917; LAS13; Red, black ink on tracing paper; detail of facine work, profile of bluff; signed; 90 x 69 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Plan of water system for vegetable garden. Estate of A.D. Lasker, Esq., 1917; LAS14; Red, black ink on linen; cross-section, plan; signed; 92 x 27 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Lasker's resubdivision, 1917; LAS15; Blueprint, pencil; plat of survey; unsigned; 75 x 77 cm; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Planting plan for bluff. A.D. Lasker, Esq., 1917; LAS16; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; signed; 92 x 41 cm; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - A topographical survey for the ravine. Estate of Mr. A.D. Lasker, 1917; LAS17; Ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; location, type of trees; signed; 100 x 48 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Plan of waterfall in ravine. Estate of A.D. Lasker, 1918; LAS18; Pencil on tracing paper; unsigned; 85 x 61 cm; Scale: 1"" = 2' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - A.D. Lasker, LAS19; Pencil on tracing paper; sketch of buildings, garden; note on verso, ""Lasker - showing location of buildings, roads, etc."" in pencil; in blue pencil, ""Void""; unsigned; 110 x 64 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Drains for vegetable garden. Estate of A.D. Lasker, LAS20; Pencil on tracing paper; signed; 87 x 33 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Topographical Map., LAS21; Blueline print; unsigned; 117 x 77 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
      - Topographical Map., LAS21a; Blueline print; unsigned; 117 x 77 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 56)
    - Lefens, T.J., Lake Geneva, Wisconsin
      - Topographical plan for part of grounds of Mr. T.J. Lefens, 1911; LEE1; Pencil, ink on linen; elevation; portion of roadway, gardens sketched in pencil; unsigned; 71 x 42 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
    - LeForgee, C.C., Decatur, Illinois
      - Contour map of C.C. LeForgee tract, 1922; LEF1; Blueprint, with house and garage cut out of white paper and pasted on; initials ""F.L.W."" below date; unsigned; 41 x 74 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - A planting plan for the grounds of Mr. C.C. LeForgee, 1923; LEF2; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; planting list gives common and botanical names and total amounts of plantings; red arrow indicates angle of photograph; notes; signed; 132 x 65 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - Contour map of C.C. LeForgee tract, 1922; LEF1; Blueprint, with house and garage cut out of white paper and pasted on; initials ""F.L.W."" below date; unsigned; 41 x 74 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - A planting plan for the grounds of Mr. C.C. LeForgee, 1923; LEF2; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; planting list gives common and botanical names and total amounts of plantings; red arrow indicates angle of photograph; notes; signed; 132 x 65 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
    - Lehmann, Augusta, Lake Villa, Illinois
      - A topo survey for the property of Miss Augusta Lehmann, 1921; LEH1; Blue, yellow, black ink; topo. lines, elevations; unsigned; 190 x 98 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
    - Leonard, Clifford M., Lake Forest, Illinois
      - General plot plan. Farm. Mr. C.M. Leonard, 1923; LEO1; Blueprint, pink pencil; buildings, drives, pond sketched in; 89 x 130 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - Plat of topographical survey of the Clifford M. Leonard estate, 1923; LEO2; Blueprint; unsigned; 115 x 85 cm; Scale: 1"" = 80' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - Untitled, 1923; LEO3; Ink, green, brown, blue pencil on tracing paper; plan of grounds, with plantings, pool, gardens, footpaths; unsigned; 85 x 105 cm; No scale (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
        (neg. # LEO3)
    - Lewiston Heights Co. Inc., Lewiston, N.Y
      - Restricted residential section and Niagara Falls Country Club, 1921; LEW1; Black, green ink on paper; lot subdivision and plan of country club and golf course; unsigned; 88 x 52 cm; Scale: 1"" = 200' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - Map of Lewiston Heights Co. Inc, 1917; LEW2; Blueline print; ""plan showing subdivision owned by...""; Bryant Fleming, landscape designer prepared map; unsigned; 81 x 61 cm; Scale: 1"" = 200' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
    - Lichtstern, Adolph J., Glencoe, Illinois (Arthur Heun, architect)
      - Grounds of Mr. A.J. Lichtstern... Topo. survey, 1915; LIC1; Ink on linen; elevations; signed; 81 x 66 cm; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 55, Folder 58)
      - Plan of topographical survey. Estate of Adolph J. Lichtstern, 1915; LIC2; Red, blue, black ink on linen; topo. lines; ""Tracing of survey by Greeley Carlson Co., 1893""; signed; 93 x 72 cm; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - Topo. survey plan for the estate of Mr. A.J. Lichtstern, 1915; LIC3; Red, black ink on linen; topo. lines; location, type of trees; pencil sketchings of roadway, etc; unsigned; 140 x 95 cm; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - A planting plan for the gardens of A.J. Lichtstern, Esq., 1916; LIC4; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; signed; 125 x 114 cm; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)
      - Plan of topographical survey. Estate of Adolph J. Lichtstern, 1916; LIC5; Blue, black ink on linen; topo. lines; signed; 97 x 75 cm; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 55, Folder 57)